{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["GABRIEL TURNER AWS DATA ENGINEER CONTACT g.turner@email.com 456-7890 Atlanta, GA LinkedIn EDUCATION Master of Science Computer Science Georgia Institute of Technology 2015 - 2017 Atlanta, GA Bachelor of Science Computer Science Georgia Institute of Technology 2009 - 2013 Atlanta, GA SKILLS AWS Lambda Presto Teradata Apache Airfow Apache Kafka PostgreSQL Looker GitHub Terraform WORK EXPERIENCE AWS Data Engineer Equifax 2019 - current / Atlanta, GA Automated infrastructure management with Terraform, reducing deployment time by 51% in the AWS environment. Analyzed data using Looker to proactively identify anomalies and limit discrepancies by 26%. Developed CI/CD pipelines using GitHub, increasing development effciency by 34% through automated testing. Designed AWS Data Pipeline workfows for effcient extraction, transformation, and loading, which reduced data processing time by 42%. Database Administrator The Home Depot 2016 - 2019 / Atlanta, GA Implemented database replication for high availability, achieving a 99.1% uptime for database systems. Managed database capacity planning to avoid performance bottlenecks and meet business needs 43% faster. Conducted regular database backups and disaster recovery strategies to minimize data loss in the event of system failures, achieving a recovery point objective of under 1 hour. Trained junior database administrators, fostering their growth and contributing to the overall team's knowledge. Data Analyst Cox Communications 2013 - 2016 / Atlanta, GA Used AWS Lambda functions to automate data processing and reduce manual effort for 34% improved effciency. Leveraged Apache Kafka for real-time data integration, reducing data latency by 52% for business applications. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to deliver data solutions that met critical business requirements. Monitored system performance with alerting mechanisms, reducing system downtime by 27%. CERTIFICATIONS AWS Certifed Big Data - Specialty",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,18,"SKILL"],[19,32,"SKILL"],[41,59,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[60,68,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[69,76,"GPE"],[78,80,"GPE"],[100,134,"EDUCATION"],[135,166,"ORG"],[167,171,"DATE"],[174,178,"DATE"],[179,186,"GPE"],[188,190,"GPE"],[191,227,"EDUCATION"],[228,259,"ORG"],[260,264,"DATE"],[267,271,"DATE"],[272,279,"GPE"],[281,283,"GPE"],[291,301,"SKILL"],[302,308,"SKILL"],[309,317,"SKILL"],[318,331,"SKILL"],[332,344,"SKILL"],[345,355,"SKILL"],[356,362,"SKILL"],[363,369,"SKILL"],[370,379,"SKILL"],[396,399,"SKILL"],[400,413,"SKILL"],[414,421,"ORG"],[422,426,"DATE"],[429,436,"DATE"],[439,446,"GPE"],[448,450,"GPE"],[492,501,"SKILL"],[531,534,"PERCENT"],[542,545,"SKILL"],[579,585,"SKILL"],[647,650,"PERCENT"],[684,690,"SKILL"],[728,731,"PERCENT"],[768,771,"SKILL"],[887,890,"PERCENT"],[892,914,"SKILL"],[915,929,"ORG"],[930,934,"DATE"],[937,941,"DATE"],[944,951,"GPE"],[953,955,"GPE"],[1024,1029,"PERCENT"],[1151,1154,"PERCENT"],[1332,1333,"CARDINAL"],[1453,1465,"SKILL"],[1466,1484,"ORG"],[1485,1489,"DATE"],[1492,1496,"DATE"],[1499,1506,"GPE"],[1508,1510,"GPE"],[1516,1526,"SKILL"],[1594,1597,"PERCENT"],[1628,1640,"SKILL"],[1698,1701,"PERCENT"],[1920,1923,"PERCENT"],[1953,1961,"SKILL"]]}]]}