{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["Ishaan Sharma 123-456-7890 – Hammond, LA – github.com/ishaansharma – linkedin.com/ishaansharma SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS Project management and consulting experience primarily focused upon nonprofit projects, requiring quick turnarounds and extensive troubleshooting Proven skills in planning, strategy development, and knowledge of customer and client business processes Excellent team-building and management skills with demonstrated success EDUCATION Southeastern Louisiana University (SLU) Hammond, LA Bachelor of Science in Computer Science May 2021 Thesis: Computerized Enrollment and Student Information Systems Major GPA: 3.84/4.00 Taylor Opportunity Program for Students Scholarship TECHNICAL SKILLS Programming Languages: Visual Basic, SQL, C, C++, Java Operating Systems: Windows NT/ 2000/ XP/ Vista, Linux, Unix Database: SQL Server, Microsoft (MS) Access, Oracle Software: JCL, SQL, DB2, MS Visio, MS Excel, MS FrontPage, MS Word RELATED EXPERIENCE Blog Writer Hammond, LA SLU Computer Science Department August 2020 – Present Designed a student portal website that allows access to blogs, research articles, and inter-office communication Wrote and published 5+ blog posts highlighting current industry trends, meeting monthly deadlines Interviewed faculty, staff, and employers ambitiously to generate content for blog posts and other relevant articles Financial Network Services, Pty Ltd. Sydney, Australia Unix Administrator Assistant June – August 2019 Operated Unix Hp/Ux 11i in the transferring of files between development and testing regions Led team of 4 to configure notebooks and install multilingual software for 6 overseas consultants Created user accounts and set permissions and passwords with UNIX - SCO PROJECT EXPERIENCE Tangi Humane Society Hammond, LA Web Programming Class January 2020 – June 2020 Served as a project team leader and developed a database to track the adoption of animals proficiently Used Visual Basic to effectively establish a new user interface that improved user experience significantly Incorporated Java, HTML, and Flash to create an interactive website LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE Pi Kappa Alpha Fraternity, Mu Nu Chapter Hammond, LA Risk Manager September 2020 – May 2021 Regulated and ensured the compliance of campus and chapter safety rules and regulations for 85 members Handled regulation violations and distribute appropriate sanctions Coordinated 2 educational programs per semester to proactively avoid possible risks Treasurer September 2019 – May 2020 Managed comprehensive budget of $55,000+ and allocated funds as needed Accurately completed all transactions and purchases to ensure proper account balances Self-Employed Lawn Service New Orleans, LA Lawn Maintenance Seasonal, Summers 2017 – 2019 Successfully established and retained customer base of 75 homes in local neighborhoods Gained advanced experience establishing a small business, including marketing, sales, and financial components HONORS & INVOLVEMENT Dean’s List (3 semesters); Presidential Scholar (2 semesters) Women in Technology (August 2019 – May 2021); Intramural Soccer (Spring 2019)",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,26,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[29,36,"GPE"],[38,40,"GPE"],[454,487,"ORG"],[494,501,"GPE"],[503,505,"GPE"],[506,545,"EDUCATION"],[546,554,"DATE"],[625,639,"GRADE"],[732,744,"SKILL"],[746,749,"SKILL"],[751,752,"SKILL"],[754,757,"SKILL"],[759,763,"SKILL"],[834,837,"SKILL"],[846,867,"SKILL"],[869,875,"ORG"],[886,889,"SKILL"],[891,894,"SKILL"],[896,899,"SKILL"],[901,909,"SKILL"],[911,919,"SKILL"],[921,933,"SKILL"],[935,942,"SKILL"],[974,981,"GPE"],[983,985,"GPE"],[986,1017,"ORG"],[1018,1029,"DATE"],[1032,1039,"DATE"],[1173,1175,"CARDINAL"],[1233,1240,"DATE"],[1368,1404,"ORG"],[1405,1411,"GPE"],[1413,1422,"GPE"],[1423,1427,"SKILL"],[1452,1456,"DATE"],[1459,1470,"DATE"],[1480,1484,"SKILL"],[1576,1577,"CARDINAL"],[1639,1640,"CARDINAL"],[1723,1727,"SKILL"],[1753,1773,"ORG"],[1774,1781,"GPE"],[1783,1785,"GPE"],[1786,1801,"SKILL"],[1808,1820,"DATE"],[1823,1832,"DATE"],[1941,1953,"SKILL"],[2057,2061,"SKILL"],[2063,2067,"SKILL"],[2073,2078,"SKILL"],[2134,2159,"ORG"],[2161,2174,"ORG"],[2175,2182,"GPE"],[2184,2186,"GPE"],[2200,2214,"DATE"],[2217,2225,"DATE"],[2318,2320,"CARDINAL"],[2408,2409,"CARDINAL"],[2490,2504,"DATE"],[2507,2515,"DATE"],[2548,2556,"MONEY"],[2700,2711,"GPE"],[2713,2715,"GPE"],[2743,2755,"DATE"],[2758,2762,"DATE"],[2818,2820,"CARDINAL"],[2918,2927,"SKILL"],[2929,2934,"SKILL"],[2995,2996,"CARDINAL"],[3031,3032,"CARDINAL"],[3065,3076,"DATE"],[3079,3087,"DATE"],[3109,3120,"DATE"]]}]]}