{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["BELLA TREVINO WEB DEVELOPER CONTACT CAREER OBJECTIVE bellatrevino@email.com 456-7890 Chicago, IL LinkedIn EDUCATION B.S. Computer Science University of Illinois Chicago 2016 - 2020 Chicago, IL GPA: 3.9 Presidential Scholarship Cum Laude Society Dean's List (6/8 semesters) SKILLS JavaScript (Angular) HTML/ CSS Python (Django) SQL (PostgreSQL, Oracle) REST APIs Git Graduate of computer science with experience working across the full-stack of software development. Looking for a role where I can grow and learn from experienced team members while drawing on project experience I have already successfully executed. WORK EXPERIENCE Web Developer Intern Book of the Month April 2019 - September 2019 / Chicago, IL Developed in-house web app using Node, React, and HTML/CSS that allowed employees to manage and recommend books Gathered user requirements, and built and maintained code for the tool, saving employees 14 monthly hours in labor Collaborated with 3 interns and senior developer to brainstorm and implement ideas and feedback into app's development Selected as the top performing intern by the technology team PROJECTS Social Media Scheduler Creator Built responsive app using Django and Node that allowed users to schedule social media posts across Instagram and Twitter Built features using scikit-learn in Python that learned the time of day of maximum engagement with social media posts, which increased overall engagement rate by 23% for users Released it for free for University of Illinois Chicago students, and it quickly grew to over 500 monthly active users Featured across 7 local newspapers, radio stations, and news networks with focus around use of Twitter and Instagram APIs Computer Science Club Co-founder April 2017 - April 2020 Presented a need for a computer science club to student government, obtained club approval, and secured club advisor Co-founded the computer science club at the University of Illinois Chicago to encourage exchanges among CS students surrounding new concepts and technical problems Led club members to spend 2 hours a week pair programming with another member to share learnings Partnered with journalism majors to attract 35 active members to the club in frst year, using web and tv campaigns",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[14,27,"SKILL"],[53,75,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[76,84,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[85,92,"GPE"],[94,96,"GPE"],[116,137,"EDUCATION"],[138,168,"ORG"],[169,173,"DATE"],[176,180,"DATE"],[181,188,"GPE"],[190,192,"GPE"],[193,201,"GRADE"],[258,261,"CARDINAL"],[280,300,"SKILL"],[301,306,"SKILL"],[307,310,"SKILL"],[311,317,"SKILL"],[319,325,"SKILL"],[327,330,"SKILL"],[332,342,"SKILL"],[344,350,"SKILL"],[352,361,"SKILL"],[362,365,"SKILL"],[430,440,"SKILL"],[444,465,"SKILL"],[632,645,"SKILL"],[653,670,"ORG"],[671,681,"DATE"],[684,698,"DATE"],[701,708,"GPE"],[710,712,"GPE"],[746,750,"SKILL"],[752,757,"SKILL"],[763,771,"SKILL"],[914,916,"CARDINAL"],[917,924,"DATE"],[958,959,"CARDINAL"],[972,988,"SKILL"],[1187,1193,"SKILL"],[1198,1202,"SKILL"],[1260,1269,"ORG"],[1274,1281,"ORG"],[1303,1315,"SKILL"],[1319,1325,"SKILL"],[1445,1448,"PERCENT"],[1484,1514,"ORG"],[1553,1556,"CARDINAL"],[1557,1564,"DATE"],[1594,1595,"CARDINAL"],[1673,1680,"ORG"],[1685,1694,"ORG"],[1733,1743,"DATE"],[1746,1756,"DATE"],[1918,1948,"ORG"],[2064,2065,"CARDINAL"],[2072,2078,"DATE"],[2179,2181,"CARDINAL"]]}]]}