{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["Emma Davis Amazon Data Scientist Dynamic data scientist with a strong foundation in machine learning, data analysis, and problem-solving. Eager to join Amazon's world-class data science team to leverage data-driven insights that drive business growth. e.davis@email.com 456-7890 San Jose, CA LinkedIn Work Experience Adobe - Data Scientist 2018 - current San Jose, CA Led data analysis initiatives that resulted in a 37% increase in customer retention rates. Developed predictive models using TensorFlow, reducing forecasting errors by 21%. Implemented Apache Hadoop to analyze large-scale datasets, improving data processing speed by 33%. Utilized Pandas and Python for data manipulation, resulting in a 2-hour reduction in data cleaning time. Cisco Systems - Junior Data Engineer 2015 - 2018 San Jose, CA Collaborated with a cross-functional team to develop ETL pipelines, improving data processing effciency by 26%. Leveraged Amazon Redshift to optimize data warehouse performance, resulting in a 3-hour reduction in query execution times. Automated data ingestion processes using AWS Glue, reducing manual effort by 32%. Conducted sentiment analysis on customer reviews using NLTK, providing valuable insights to the marketing team. eBay - Trainee Data Analyst 2012 - 2015 San Jose, CA Set up Kafka clusters and integrated data sources, resulting in a 30% improvement in data processing effciency. Achieved a $4K reduction in infrastructure costs by containerizing data processing components. Spearheaded automated deployment scripts and version control using Git, resulting in a 27% decrease in deployment errors. Used Python and SQL to clean and preprocess data, achieving a data quality improvement of 18%. Education Stanford University - Bachelor of Science, Computer Science 2008 - 2012 Stanford, CA Skills Python; Pandas; TensorFlow; Apache Hadoop; Amazon Redshift; AWS; NLTK; Apache Kafka; Git; Docker",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[11,17,"ORG"],[18,32,"SKILL"],[41,55,"SKILL"],[84,100,"SKILL"],[102,115,"SKILL"],[121,137,"SKILL"],[152,158,"ORG"],[173,185,"SKILL"],[252,269,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[270,278,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[279,287,"GPE"],[289,291,"GPE"],[317,322,"ORG"],[325,339,"SKILL"],[340,344,"DATE"],[347,354,"DATE"],[355,363,"GPE"],[365,367,"GPE"],[417,420,"PERCENT"],[493,503,"SKILL"],[536,539,"PERCENT"],[553,566,"SKILL"],[635,638,"PERCENT"],[649,655,"SKILL"],[660,666,"SKILL"],[671,688,"SKILL"],[725,738,"SKILL"],[745,758,"SKILL"],[768,781,"SKILL"],[782,786,"DATE"],[789,793,"DATE"],[794,802,"GPE"],[804,806,"GPE"],[914,917,"PERCENT"],[929,944,"SKILL"],[1084,1092,"SKILL"],[1120,1123,"PERCENT"],[1180,1184,"SKILL"],[1252,1264,"SKILL"],[1265,1269,"DATE"],[1272,1276,"DATE"],[1277,1285,"GPE"],[1287,1289,"GPE"],[1356,1359,"PERCENT"],[1413,1416,"MONEY"],[1564,1567,"SKILL"],[1584,1587,"PERCENT"],[1624,1630,"SKILL"],[1635,1638,"SKILL"],[1709,1712,"PERCENT"],[1724,1743,"ORG"],[1746,1783,"EDUCATION"],[1784,1788,"DATE"],[1791,1795,"DATE"],[1796,1804,"ORG"],[1806,1808,"GPE"],[1816,1822,"SKILL"],[1824,1830,"SKILL"],[1832,1842,"SKILL"],[1844,1857,"SKILL"],[1859,1874,"SKILL"],[1876,1879,"SKILL"],[1881,1885,"SKILL"],[1887,1899,"SKILL"],[1901,1904,"SKILL"],[1906,1912,"SKILL"]]}]]}