{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["LANDON WINSLOW Computer Engineer l.winslow@email.com (123) 456-7890 Malvern, PA LinkedIn EDUCATION Bachelor of Science Electrical and Computer Engineering Carnegie Mellon University 2008 - 2012 Pittsburgh, PA SKILLS Visual Studio Code Git Xilinx Vivado MATLAB AutoCAD VHDL Wireshark Arduino IDE VMware JUnit WORK EXPERIENCE Computer Engineer Siemens Healthineers 2018 - current Malvern, PA Designed and implemented software enhancements using Visual Studio Code, resulting in a 67% reduction in system response time Leveraged Git for version control and achieved a 98% codebase accuracy rate Optimized FPGA designs with Xilinx Vivado, leading to an 89% decrease in resource utilization while maintaining system performance Developed MATLAB scripts for data analysis, which improved data processing speed by 63% and enhancing overall data accuracy Systems Analyst PPG Industries 2015 - 2018 Pittsburgh, PA Conducted comprehensive system analysis, identifying and rectifying inefciencies, which led to a 76% improvement in workfow efciency Collaborated with cross-functional teams to implement Wireshark network monitoring, reducing network downtime by 72% Integrated Arduino IDE for automated equipment control, resulting in a 27% reduction in production errors Assisted in the migration to VMware virtualization and reducing hardware costs by 18% and enhancing scalability IT Support Specialist UPMC 2012 - 2015 Pittsburgh, PA Implemented JUnit testing framework that improved software reliability and reducing critical bugs by 64% Utilized AutoCAD to create detailed technical drawings, contributing to a 74% increase in design precision and manufacturability Employed VHDL-based hardware modules, which resulted in a 76% reduction in power consumption and enhanced system reliability Managed and maintained VMware virtualization infrastructure, ensuring 99.9% uptime for critical systems",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,32,"SKILL"],[33,52,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[53,67,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[68,75,"GPE"],[77,79,"GPE"],[99,154,"EDUCATION"],[155,181,"ORG"],[182,186,"DATE"],[189,193,"DATE"],[194,204,"GPE"],[206,208,"GPE"],[216,234,"SKILL"],[235,238,"SKILL"],[239,252,"SKILL"],[253,259,"SKILL"],[260,267,"SKILL"],[268,272,"SKILL"],[273,282,"SKILL"],[283,294,"SKILL"],[295,301,"SKILL"],[302,307,"SKILL"],[324,341,"SKILL"],[342,362,"ORG"],[363,367,"DATE"],[370,377,"DATE"],[378,385,"GPE"],[387,389,"GPE"],[443,461,"SKILL"],[478,481,"PERCENT"],[526,529,"SKILL"],[565,568,"PERCENT"],[620,633,"SKILL"],[649,652,"PERCENT"],[733,739,"SKILL"],[807,810,"PERCENT"],[847,862,"SKILL"],[863,877,"ORG"],[878,882,"DATE"],[885,889,"DATE"],[890,900,"GPE"],[902,904,"GPE"],[1002,1005,"PERCENT"],[1092,1101,"SKILL"],[1151,1154,"PERCENT"],[1166,1177,"SKILL"],[1226,1229,"PERCENT"],[1290,1296,"SKILL"],[1343,1346,"PERCENT"],[1373,1394,"SKILL"],[1395,1399,"ORG"],[1400,1404,"DATE"],[1407,1411,"DATE"],[1412,1422,"GPE"],[1424,1426,"GPE"],[1439,1444,"SKILL"],[1528,1531,"PERCENT"],[1541,1548,"SKILL"],[1606,1609,"PERCENT"],[1670,1680,"SKILL"],[1719,1722,"PERCENT"],[1809,1815,"SKILL"],[1856,1861,"PERCENT"]]}]]}