{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["GABRIEL RAMIREZ Data Scientist Machine Learning Engineer g.ramirez@email.com (123) 456-7890 Blue Bell, PA LinkedIn EDUCATION Master's degree Statistics Carnegie Mellon University 2011 - 2013 Blue Bell, PA Bachelor of Science Statistics Carnegie Mellon University 2007 - 2011 Pittsburgh, PA SKILLS NumPy Scikit-learn ggplot2 dplyr MySQL SQLite Keras PyTorch CERTIFICATIONS Certifed Machine Learning Engineer (CMLE) WORK EXPERIENCE Data Scientist Machine Learning Engineer Siemens Digital Industries 2019 - current Blue Bell, PA Analyzed customer churn by developing predictive models, leading to a 12% reduction within 4 months. Wrangled data using dplyr, which resulted in a 33% faster preprocessing time that enabled additional insight extraction from large datasets. Created deep learning models with Keras for natural language processing tasks and improved sentiment analysis accuracy by 61%. Reduced forecasting errors by 18% by using time series models with Scikit-learn. Machine Learning Specialist Cognizant 2016 - 2019 Pittsburgh, PA Implemented deep learning architectures with PyTorch for computer vision tasks, achieving a 42% reduction in false positives and negatives in object detection algorithms. Conducted A/B testing on machine learning models to identify an optimal model confguration that led to an 11% user retention increase. Streamlined the model deployment process by creating automated pipelines using CI/CD tools, which reduced deployment time by 52%. Applied transfer learning techniques to adapt pre-trained models to specifc domains, reducing training time for new projects by 23%. Machine Learning Engineer Covestro 2013 - 2016 Pittsburgh, PA Developed machine learning models using NumPy to achieve an average accuracy improvement of 12% over baseline models. Leveraged ggplot2 to create insightful data visualizations that resulted in 21% less time spent on data preprocessing tasks. Designed MySQL databases to effciently handle large-scale datasets, lowering query response time by 54%. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to build a recommendation system using fltering techniques, which increased user engagement by 32%.",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,30,"SKILL"],[31,47,"SKILL"],[57,76,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[77,91,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[92,101,"GPE"],[103,105,"GPE"],[125,151,"EDUCATION"],[152,178,"ORG"],[179,183,"DATE"],[186,190,"DATE"],[191,200,"GPE"],[202,204,"GPE"],[205,235,"EDUCATION"],[236,262,"ORG"],[263,267,"DATE"],[270,274,"DATE"],[275,285,"GPE"],[287,289,"GPE"],[297,302,"SKILL"],[303,315,"SKILL"],[316,323,"SKILL"],[324,329,"SKILL"],[330,335,"SKILL"],[336,342,"SKILL"],[343,348,"SKILL"],[349,356,"SKILL"],[381,397,"SKILL"],[430,444,"SKILL"],[445,461,"SKILL"],[471,497,"ORG"],[498,502,"DATE"],[505,512,"DATE"],[513,522,"GPE"],[524,526,"GPE"],[597,600,"PERCENT"],[618,627,"DATE"],[648,653,"SKILL"],[675,678,"PERCENT"],[777,790,"SKILL"],[803,808,"SKILL"],[813,840,"SKILL"],[891,894,"PERCENT"],[926,929,"PERCENT"],[963,976,"SKILL"],[977,993,"SKILL"],[1005,1014,"ORG"],[1015,1019,"DATE"],[1022,1026,"DATE"],[1027,1037,"GPE"],[1039,1041,"GPE"],[1054,1067,"SKILL"],[1087,1094,"SKILL"],[1099,1114,"SKILL"],[1134,1137,"PERCENT"],[1238,1254,"SKILL"],[1319,1322,"PERCENT"],[1473,1476,"PERCENT"],[1606,1609,"PERCENT"],[1611,1627,"SKILL"],[1637,1645,"ORG"],[1646,1650,"DATE"],[1653,1657,"DATE"],[1658,1668,"GPE"],[1670,1672,"GPE"],[1683,1699,"SKILL"],[1713,1718,"SKILL"],[1765,1768,"PERCENT"],[1801,1808,"SKILL"],[1830,1849,"SKILL"],[1867,1870,"PERCENT"],[1925,1930,"SKILL"],[2016,2019,"PERCENT"],[2157,2160,"PERCENT"]]}]]}