{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["BARRETT LARAMIE Computer Scientist Ebar@email.com (123) 456-7890 Greer, SC LinkedIn Github EDUCATION B.S. Computer Science Bob Jones University September 2014 - June 2018 Greenville, SC GPA: 3.8 SKILLS Computer System Building and Repair Hardware and Software Installation Diagnostic Software Utilities, Remote Access, Networking, Computer Management CNNs LSTMs PyTorch WORK EXPERIENCE Computer Scientist Collins Aerospace December 2020 - current Remote Managed 100% of system and network procurement, installation, administration, and security Designed and implemented 4 new custom tools and methods to troubleshoot and modify 12 existing tools Developed and used computing environments for analysis Provided technical assistance in conducting 215+ interviews, searches, and other investigative and operational activities Drafted 40+ documents on technical and other professional matters in varying degrees of diffculty Utilized machine learning best practices to drive system automation, software quality, and development of 4 internal research teams Machine Learning Scientist Aeronix Inc. November 2019 - December 2020 Greenville, SC Designed 17+ Deep Learning and Computer Vision algorithms to detect objects of interest, issues, and defects Developed and implemented 8 Machine Learning models and techniques to solve 11 business problems, saving $56,000+ Evaluated the accuracy and quality of 210+ data sources and designed models Maintained and improved skill profciency levels within the modeling, technology, and industry best practices Entry-Level Computer Support Specialist Netalytics June 2018 - November 2019 Greer, SC Analyzed 410+ computer and network-related problems reported by end-users Identifed, troubleshot, and resolved 360+ hardware, software, and network-related problems Established a new tracking system to log requests, monitor progress, track problem resolutions, and identify 100% of failure patterns Communicated with 12+ supervisors and managers regarding unresolved issues and ineffcient tracking Maintained inventory of deployed, loaned, recycled, and stored IT equipment (over 3,000 units)",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,34,"SKILL"],[35,49,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[50,64,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[65,70,"GPE"],[72,74,"GPE"],[84,90,"SKILL"],[101,122,"EDUCATION"],[123,143,"ORG"],[144,158,"DATE"],[161,170,"DATE"],[171,181,"GPE"],[183,185,"GPE"],[186,194,"GRADE"],[202,237,"SKILL"],[238,272,"SKILL"],[273,302,"SKILL"],[304,317,"SKILL"],[319,329,"SKILL"],[331,350,"SKILL"],[351,355,"SKILL"],[356,361,"SKILL"],[362,369,"SKILL"],[386,404,"SKILL"],[405,422,"ORG"],[423,436,"DATE"],[439,446,"DATE"],[462,466,"PERCENT"],[570,571,"CARDINAL"],[628,630,"CARDINAL"],[745,749,"CARDINAL"],[831,834,"CARDINAL"],[1027,1028,"CARDINAL"],[1053,1069,"SKILL"],[1080,1092,"ORG"],[1093,1106,"DATE"],[1109,1122,"DATE"],[1123,1133,"GPE"],[1135,1137,"GPE"],[1147,1150,"CARDINAL"],[1151,1164,"SKILL"],[1169,1184,"SKILL"],[1273,1274,"CARDINAL"],[1275,1291,"SKILL"],[1323,1325,"CARDINAL"],[1352,1360,"MONEY"],[1399,1403,"CARDINAL"],[1558,1585,"SKILL"],[1586,1596,"ORG"],[1597,1606,"DATE"],[1609,1622,"DATE"],[1623,1628,"GPE"],[1630,1632,"GPE"],[1642,1646,"CARDINAL"],[1744,1748,"CARDINAL"],[1907,1911,"PERCENT"],[1950,1953,"CARDINAL"],[2113,2118,"CARDINAL"]]}]]}