{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["STEFAN BUCHHOLZ Data Analytics Engineer stefan.buchholz@email.com (123) 456-7890 Raleigh, NC LinkedIn WORK EXPERIENCE Data Analytics Engineer Oculus 2019 - current Raleigh, NC Managed 100% of continuous integration and continuous deployment-based initiatives Collaborated with 3 product teams tasked to create premier member experiences using AWS Created and updated technical documentation such as source mapping documents and data dictionaries Managed 55,000+ datasets to track data lineage, ensure data quality, and improve data discoverability Designed and implemented 5 data model changes to align with updated industry standards Data & Analytics Consultant KPMG 2018 - 2019 Raleigh, NC Translated business needs into technical specifcations to deliver 4 customized reporting systems Built 17 data pipelines and infrastructures to support the needs of machine learning and analytics Designed, built, and maintained 100% of automated systems for reporting, analysis, and analytics Identifed and interpreted trends, patterns, and correlations among 100+ data points Data Analytics Engineer Harbor Freight Tools 2015 - 2018 Raleigh, NC Collaborated with 6 business stakeholders to analyze business processes and recommend technical solutions Defned data standards that enabled >70% more effcient and effective decision making Developed, documented, and implemented 20+ data analysis, analytics, and reporting solutions Supported the development of 7 dashboards and models pertaining to connectivity and visualization of IOT data EDUCATION Bachelor's of Science Computer Science Duke University 2011 - 2015 Durham, NC SKILLS Python Numpy Matplotlib Snowfake AWS TensorFlow R SQL Jupyter Notebook NoSQL",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,30,"SKILL"],[40,65,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[66,80,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[81,88,"GPE"],[90,92,"GPE"],[118,132,"SKILL"],[142,148,"ORG"],[149,153,"DATE"],[156,163,"DATE"],[164,171,"GPE"],[173,175,"GPE"],[184,188,"PERCENT"],[277,278,"CARDINAL"],[343,346,"SKILL"],[454,461,"CARDINAL"],[573,574,"CARDINAL"],[635,651,"SKILL"],[663,667,"ORG"],[668,672,"DATE"],[675,679,"DATE"],[680,687,"GPE"],[689,691,"GPE"],[758,759,"CARDINAL"],[795,797,"CARDINAL"],[857,873,"SKILL"],[920,924,"PERCENT"],[1052,1056,"CARDINAL"],[1069,1083,"SKILL"],[1093,1113,"ORG"],[1114,1118,"DATE"],[1121,1125,"DATE"],[1126,1133,"GPE"],[1135,1137,"GPE"],[1156,1157,"CARDINAL"],[1280,1283,"PERCENT"],[1367,1370,"CARDINAL"],[1371,1384,"SKILL"],[1450,1451,"CARDINAL"],[1522,1525,"SKILL"],[1541,1579,"EDUCATION"],[1580,1595,"ORG"],[1596,1600,"DATE"],[1603,1607,"DATE"],[1608,1614,"GPE"],[1616,1618,"GPE"],[1626,1632,"SKILL"],[1633,1638,"SKILL"],[1639,1649,"SKILL"],[1650,1658,"SKILL"],[1659,1662,"SKILL"],[1663,1673,"SKILL"],[1674,1675,"SKILL"],[1676,1679,"SKILL"],[1680,1696,"SKILL"],[1697,1702,"SKILL"]]}]]}