{"classes":["PERSON","ORG","GPE","DATE","PERCENT","MONEY","CARDINAL","CONTACT NUMBER","EMAIL ADDRESS","SKILL","EDUCATION","GRADE"],"annotations":[["ALEXANDER OWENS Data Science Consultant alex.owens@email.com (123) 456-7890 Seattle, WA LinkedIn WORK EXPERIENCE Data Science Manager Zillow Group October 2018 - current Seattle, WA Reduced decision-making time by 18% by implementing Tableau dashboards, providing key metrics to senior managers Executed A/B testing experiments to evaluate the efectiveness of diferent pricing strategies that boosted revenue by 17% Boosted team productivity by conducting regular performance evaluations and mentoring junior data scientists Automated data extraction and transformation processes via SQL and Databricks, reducing data processing time by 31% Data Scientist T-Mobile US, Inc. May 2014 - August 2018 Bellevue, WA Implemented Apache Spark workfows for large-scale data processing and reduced data processing time by 34% Developed machine learning models via Scikit-learn to optimize pricing strategies for an 11% increase in revenue Decreased data access latency by 32% by leveraging Databricks to optimize data storage and retrieval Cut incident response time by 18% with Apache Spark streaming for real-time anomaly detection in network data Data Analyst Expedia Group April 2010 - April 2014 Bellevue, WA Used Informatica for data integration and improved data consistency across multiple platforms by 41% Developed a natural language processing (NLP) system with NLTK, resulting in a 39% reduction in manual text analysis Managed a large-scale data migration project using Informatica and ensured zero downtime plus a smooth transition for stakeholders Spearheaded the development of a churn prediction model using Scikit-learn that reduced customer attrition by 8% EDUCATION B.S. Data Science University of Washington September 2006 - April 2010 Seattle, WA SKILLS SQL Tableau Scikit-learn Apache Spark SQL (Structured Query Language) Databricks NLTK (Natural Language Toolkit) Informatica",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,28,"SKILL"],[40,60,"EMAIL ADDRESS"],[61,75,"CONTACT NUMBER"],[76,83,"GPE"],[85,87,"GPE"],[113,125,"SKILL"],[134,146,"ORG"],[147,159,"DATE"],[162,169,"DATE"],[170,177,"GPE"],[179,181,"GPE"],[214,217,"PERCENT"],[234,241,"SKILL"],[412,415,"PERCENT"],[509,524,"SKILL"],[535,550,"SKILL"],[584,587,"SKILL"],[592,602,"SKILL"],[637,640,"PERCENT"],[641,655,"SKILL"],[656,673,"ORG"],[674,682,"DATE"],[685,696,"DATE"],[697,705,"GPE"],[707,709,"GPE"],[722,734,"SKILL"],[812,815,"PERCENT"],[826,842,"SKILL"],[854,866,"SKILL"],[905,908,"PERCENT"],[962,965,"PERCENT"],[980,990,"SKILL"],[1060,1063,"PERCENT"],[1069,1081,"SKILL"],[1140,1152,"SKILL"],[1153,1166,"ORG"],[1167,1177,"DATE"],[1180,1190,"DATE"],[1191,1199,"GPE"],[1201,1203,"GPE"],[1301,1304,"PERCENT"],[1317,1344,"SKILL"],[1346,1349,"SKILL"],[1363,1367,"SKILL"],[1384,1387,"PERCENT"],[1473,1484,"SKILL"],[1615,1627,"SKILL"],[1663,1665,"PERCENT"],[1676,1693,"EDUCATION"],[1694,1718,"ORG"],[1719,1733,"DATE"],[1736,1746,"DATE"],[1747,1754,"GPE"],[1756,1758,"GPE"],[1766,1769,"SKILL"],[1770,1777,"SKILL"],[1778,1790,"SKILL"],[1791,1803,"SKILL"],[1804,1807,"SKILL"],[1809,1834,"SKILL"],[1836,1846,"SKILL"],[1847,1851,"SKILL"],[1853,1877,"SKILL"],[1879,1890,"SKILL"]]}]]}